(Raj:)You know who's got to be
the bravest person
(Raj:)in the Marvel Universe?
(Raj:)Whoever has to give
She-Hulk a bikini wax.
(Howard:)You want to talk brave,
(Howard:)how about Captain America's
undocumented Mexican gardener?
(Leonard:)He's not braver than
(Leonard:)whoever uses the bathroom
after The Thing?
(Sheldon:)As usual, you're all wrong.
(Raj:)The bravest person
in the Marvel Universe
(Sheldon:)is the doctor who gives
Wolverine his prostate exam.
(Howard:)How about the guy who gets
(Howard:)a prostate exam from Wolverine?
Now you're just being silly.
(Sheldon:)Wolverine's never displayed
(Sheldon:)the slightest interest
in helping others
(Sheldon:)prevent prostate cancer.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)Yes, the elevator's
out of order;
(Sheldon:)you'll have to use the stairs.
(Sheldon:)Of course you can.
(Sheldon:)Pizza dates back
to the 16th century,
(Sheldon:)while the first elevator
was not installed until 1852.
(Sheldon:)That means that
for over 300 years,
(Sheldon:)people carried pizzas up stairs.